Jay
If you don't tell me, I will stay under the water.
And I can't swim
Yu Seqi
Yu Seqi, wake up
Seulgi
I know you deliberately failed the final exam
You want your dad to help you get the Demon King-level exam questions?
This way you have a chance to take revenge
revenge
why should i do that
You seem to have misunderstood
Then why did you save me?
You said...
Have you ever imagined me dying?
That means for you
i am special
That's why you just jumped into the water to save me
We are on the same side, right?
You clearly know...
Why did you agree to get the test questions?
are you crazy
Because I don't want to see you...
To send dad to jail
ruin your life
My life has been ruined long ago
I'm already living in hell, it can't get any worse
Revenge…
What kind of person do you think I am...
Will you sacrifice yourself for others?
that's why
it's for myself
Because I want to live
So please don't mind your own business
No
Anyway, your dad...
I also read your mind
That's why I got involved
He thought that as long as he got me involved
You don’t dare to act rashly
What else should I do?
You continue to look down on me like you are now
And then use me...
Get the Demon King-level exam questions
Don't
What you did was a crime but I'm the victim's daughter.
If you want to get the title, collect evidence
can only do this
Your father will take it lightly if you use me as bait.
Yu Seqi…
Since we have to do
Just do it thoroughly
Don't let him regret it
Well, since we have to do it, why not do it more thoroughly?
Lest she regret it later
How about letting her talk about it herself?
Collect evidence by the way
Jay
[Plan B]
My dad actually agreed to let you find the question committee member
It's so suspicious
He must have other plans
[List of committee members who proposed the question: Park Myung-ho]
Mr. Park Minghao
When is your birthday?
August 9, 1973
OK
[Medical staff duty schedule]
Dad sent people from the hospital to the question dormitory
[Jay]
Teacher where are you now
[Power off]
He will definitely use a different method than last year
Seulgi, you might be in danger
basic elements of conversation
A dialogue or sentence of two or more sentences
Conversation means oral expression
Sentences are written communication
Don't worry about the rest
Just leave it to me
Conversation or sentence of more than two consecutive sentences
to form a conversation
Everyone must remember this
Good
It shouldn't be difficult
Not difficult
Then let's talk about it
Direct dialogue and indirect dialogue
What are you going to do alone?
And why did you entrust Jieyin to Xiaojing?
You also know that my dad uses
The camera around Jieyin's neck
Come and spy on us
The countdown on your tablet
Is it the day when results are announced?
Yeah
Seulgi
What's wrong
Even if there are no devil-level exam questions
You will definitely do well in the exam too
You will be admitted to the medical department of a Korean university as you wish
Everyone, get the registration form
I must hand it back today
So no matter what happens
You must never give up on the entrance exam
Your registration form…
I've already paid it for you
Also
I want to tell you a secret
In fact, the medicine I gave you during the midterm exam...
Just vitamins
I was shocked when you called
I thought we would never meet again
Forget it, if you don’t know, just pretend I didn’t say it.
You say it
[Court]
3408…
It was that bastard Liu Taejun who ordered me to
Said it was a trading condition
Here it is
What are you looking for me for?
How much money can you make selling medicine?
If you want to share it with Zhu Yili
You shouldn't make much money, right?
I have a business that makes more money
Do you want to try it?
Students here take medicine to stay up late studying
In that case, why not just sell college entrance exam questions?
You girl, who allowed you to show off in front of Guan Gong?
Am I kidding?
Liu Taijun of J Medical Center does this
Isn't it because of his daughter?
It records that he and his daughter
VIP customer list for buying medicines
By the way, they are all children from prominent families.
Then you can make whatever price you want
what should i do first
thank you
If it's not enough, I can give it to you again
It actually succeeded
You can use these for college tuition.
I heard that the tuition fees for the medical department are very expensive.
I will come first in the exam and get a scholarship
Then this time it must be successful no matter what.
you know
[Model student]
Why are you in such a hurry?
In fact, I have nothing but medicine on my hands
There is something better
But because of your mother, I have to be careful
no problem
Come and take a look
what are you doing
Plans changed
is acute compartment syndrome
An emergency fasciotomy has been performed
But the patient's blood pressure is now too low
Need platelet concentrate
Please contact the partner hospital quickly
Ask them to send blood bags and anesthetics, quickly.
You can't bring things in from outside
He needs type O Rh negative blood
There's no blood available here
If it drags on for another 6 hours, his muscles and nerves will
All will die
Hurry up
Let's go
Yes
Thank you for your hard work
Let’s go. Expect to arrive at 10 o’clock.
[Dad]
Driver, please drive faster
There's no need to be in such a hurry, Dean
There are no patients in the car
[3 hours ago]
It's so nerve-wracking
Do you want one too?
I've quit
Get off…
Yu Seqi
in his right pocket
Seulgi
give me that thing
Hello Yu Seqi
You wake up
Seulgi, please
Don’t you also need Demon King-level exam questions?
How can you get into a Korean university without that?
How to be a doctor
Are you going to give everything up to this woman?
don't worry
I won't give it to her
Damn it
Seulgi…
sorry
[University entrance exam starts 10 hours ago]
[Are you sure you will give us a question? Please reply as soon as possible]
what are you waiting for
Take out the test questions quickly
Dad
This is it
I'm not going to operate on her
What nonsense are you talking about?
Those who need the Demon King-level exam questions in Seulgi’s belly
It's not me, it's you...
And my daughter Jay
What to do now
Go find another doctor quickly
I'll do it
what
I said I would hold the knife
good idea
Doing this will be of great help to your study
you all are crazy
scalpel
well done
Why haven't you come out yet...
He came out...
Come
Queue first
Come one by one
Get in line, don't rush
OK…
-You're not lying, are you?
-Of course
Give it to us quickly
Just as I expected
My daughter is indeed gifted
You will definitely become an excellent doctor in the future
Does my sister have no choice like me?
That’s why I killed Teacher Dohyuk.
Seulgi probably won't wake up until noon tomorrow
I said...
I won't be the one to destroy her
but you
How could...
The topic is different
[Zhu Yili]
[Yu Seqi]
The university entrance exam for the 2025 academic year will be held on the morning of the 14th
Held in 1,275 examination rooms in 85 examination areas across the country
[More than 503,000 people across the country took the exam...
The number of people decreased compared with last year]
The number of people taking the exam this year is 503,215
1,588 fewer people than last year
Thank you for your hard work
How did you do in the exam?
You sneaked out of the back door, so you probably failed the exam, right?
don't blame me
This is your strength
What a madman
what are you doing
let me go
I still have technical exams to take.
Technical examination
Do you know that I am because of you?
How miserable it was to be scolded by President Jiang
When you make money, you just want to pat your butt and leave.
Get in the car for me
According to Article 14 of the Child and Adolescent Sexual Protection Act
Those who induce or persuade young people to participate in the sex trade
Will be sentenced to fixed-term imprisonment of not more than 7 years
or a fine of not more than 50 million won
(Note: Approximately NT$1.06 million)
who are you get out of the way
In accordance with the provisions of Article 14
Minors will not be sentenced
Do you want to go to the police station together?
It seems you really left the hotel
Really
(Note: Approximately NT$210,000)
She wants me to sell my first time for 10 million
what
What's your expression?
Why are you so surprised?
You…
Haven't done it yet?
Yeah
Then why do you have to study medicine?
You really don't want to open or lift any pot.
No matter how I look at it, I think you are more suitable for the law department.
You were so handsome just now
Is your wrist okay?
Don’t you still want to take the academic exam?
Anyway, I will definitely not be able to get into college with my strength.
But you have to play the harp at least once in the examination room.
Isn't it?
Come here you bastard
Our child failed in the exam and you have to take responsibility.
Come here
[Three weeks later]
[Application for withdrawal from school]
You didn't go to the exam. I'm still wondering where you were hiding.
Are you planning to drop out of school?
You know you have to get your diploma before you can retake the exam, right?
Teacher Jin
why are you still here
Come to the classroom quickly
Good
We'll talk about this later
Liu Jieyi
congratulations
Congratulations on getting perfect scores
Which department do you plan to apply for?
I heard that the difficulty of this year’s exam is at a record high
You are the only candidate with perfect scores in the country
What is your secret to reading?
Especially in mathematics, everyone says the questions are difficult
Did you ever think you would do so well in the exam?
In fact, I already knew
As long as you fill in the answer card correctly
I will definitely get full marks
I plan to apply for the Department of Medicine at a Korean University
Following in my father's footsteps
become a doctor
This is the power of genes, right?
Congratulations to Dr. Liu Taijun of J Medical Center
thank you
Your daughter is the only one in the country who got a perfect score in the college entrance examination
how are you feeling now
There is something about the efforts of the past nineteen years
The feeling of finally being rewarded
Yes
After all, there is such a thing as entering a higher school
Parents and children need to work together
What's your secret?
Do you want your daughter to be number one in the country?
If I say I didn't do anything in particular
People may be angry
-But I'm actually just like any other parent...
- so funny
Try to let her eat a nutritionally balanced diet
Give her lots of love and support
[The exclusive secret to getting perfect scores in college exams]
But I guess the most important thing is...
I believe my daughter will do well in the exam
[The unknown secret behind the perfect score in the college entrance examination]
Sister, let’s get ready to go to kindergarten.
The weather is a bit cold today
Can you bear it?
Jay, how were you feeling at that time?
It's fear...
It’s fear…
Or...
You are actually very happy
What's wrong
what happened
The dean’s daughter committed suicide by jumping into the river
How could it be
Liu Jieyi?
What's going on
Is she still on live broadcast?
What are you doing? Please put subtitles.
Just received the latest news
Get full marks on the university entrance exam
Liu, a classmate from "A Girls' High School in Jiangnan"
I just committed suicide by drowning myself in the river.
I repeat it again
Student Liu got perfect scores in the university entrance exam
[Flash report: A girl from a certain girls’ high school in Jiangnan got perfect marks in the college entrance examination
Student Liu just committed suicide by throwing himself into the river]
I just committed suicide by drowning myself in the river.
Borrow it
Officer, how is the search progress now?
Let’s talk about it later
-Borrowed it
-Have you found anyone yet?
Found it
here
Snap shot…
Sister Jina
She…
really alive
Where is Jay? Where is Jay?
We will continue to search
Miss, what's your name?
please tell me your name
Please help me find Jay
Hurry up
Please...
I should have noticed it then
Jay
Which season is your heart going through?
Liu, the director of a well-known medical center in Jiangnan
Suspected of illegally stealing college entrance exams for his children
Difficult questions in mathematics
Not only did he steal the 2025 exam questions
Also stole the 2024 exam questions
Even killing one in the process
Question committee member named Yu
he came out
Mr. Liu Taijun…
Your eldest daughter is obviously still alive
Why do you say she is dead?
The victim's family thinks you're trying to cover it up
The facts of the murder. What's your version?
For the second daughter who jumped off the building after revealing everything
do you have anything to say
As long as you don't see the body
I will keep looking
Do you understand what dad means?
Okay, let's go
Mr. Liu Taijun...please say a few words...
[Six months later]
-Please thoroughly investigate the truth about the entrance examination case
-The weather is so hot, let’s have some ice...
My daughter doesn't want to be interviewed
The weather is so hot. You should go back.
It was revealed that she was captured in the video
She went to see Park Minghao
He was even sent to the operating room
Her friends…
missing
Are you polite?
Jay
we are still waiting for you
welcome
Give me some more radish kimchi
good
Zhu Yili works part-time
While thinking about the future direction
Would you like to order a meal?
You are more beautiful in person than in the photos
you know who i am
But it seems that I want to live a low-key life...
She probably has no chance in this life
Cui Jing was recommended by Ye Li
Choose the Department of Law
But…
she is still single
it's so cute
how old is it
Because I'm busy studying law
She has no time to look at men at all
Let's go
Probably before graduation
She doesn't even want to fall in love, right?
Cui Jing
wait for me
[Renren Adult Products Store]
That person is just like an earthbound spirit
Is Jai's father still out there?
Yeah
Should we just move?
So what if I move?
Will he find us yet?
Ignore him
Not even convicted of murder
After a few months in jail, he was released
Still haven't let us go yet
I passed the High School Academic Ability Supervision Examination
Currently preparing for the university entrance exam
[College Entrance Examination Countdown to 7 Days]
After not taking medicine
Less time to study
But my mind is much clearer than before
I always feel that if I fall asleep, the exam will be over.
So I can only sit and take a nap
But I only slept for a while
I actually had a dream
Jay
[University Entrance Examination Countdown to 1 Day]